(Sheldon:)I've invented a science joke,
would you like to hear it?
(Amy:)Sure.
(Sheldon:)How many Edisons does it take
to screw in a light bulb?
(Amy:)How many?
(Sheldon:)Who cares?
He stole the idea
(Sheldon:)and doesn't deserve
his own joke.
(Amy:)Is that really true?
(Sheldon:)Of course, that's how you know
it's a good joke.
(Sheldon:)It not only entertains,
it informs.
Hey, sorry
to interrupt.
(Sheldon:)Uh, Barry,
(Sheldon:)uh, how many Edisons does it
take to screw in a light bulb?
(Barry:)Did you know Edison didn't
actually invent the light bulb?
(Sheldon:)What do you want,
Barry?
Just wanted to drop this off
as a little thank you for Amy.
(Amy:)What's this for?
Your idea really
helped me out.
My light-cone quantization
paper's online already.
The response
has been amazing.
(Amy:)Well, that's
fascinating.
(Amy:)I can't wait to read it.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, me as well.
(Sheldon:)Uh, please e-mail it
to Sheldon@Bazinga.biz.
Why "dot-biz"?
(Sheldon:)Because I just gave
you the business.